Sometimes it can be useful to join a table onto itself.
من المفيد أحياناً ربط جدول بنفسه.
Most of the time, you'll do this in order to find cases where
في أغلب الأوقات، ستقوم بذلك لتجد حالات
two events both occur one after another.
يقع فيها حدثان واحداً تلو الآخر.
For example, imagine you want to know which accounts made multiple orders within 30 days.
مثلاً، تخيّل أنك تريد أن تعرف أي الحسابات تم فيها شراء عدة طلبات في غضون 30 يوماً.
One way to do this, would be to join the orders table onto
إحدى طرق القيام بذلك هي ربط جدول الطلبات
itself with an inequality join.
بنفسه بعملية الربط بعدم المساواة.
Let's quickly walk through the logic in this join because it's a little bit complicated.
لنشرح سريعاً منطق عملية الربط هذه لأنه معقد بعض الشيء.
First, we want to make sure that we're joining on the same account.
أولاً، علينا التأكد من أننا نقوم بالربط على الحساب نفسه.
So, in the first orders table,
لذا، في جدول الطلبات الأول،
which we've labeled o1,
الذي رمزنا له بالرمز o1،
we'll look up the account ID and compare it to
سنبحث عن معرف الحساب ونقارنه
the account ID in the second orders table o2.
بمعرف الحساب في جدول الطلبات الثاني "o2".
It's really the same table.
إنه الجدول نفسه في واقع الأمر،
We're just joining it to itself and giving it a different alias.
ولكننا نربطه بنفسه ونعطيه اسماً مستعاراً مختلفاً.
Since we want the records in o2 to be within 28 days after the records in o1,
بما أننا نريد أن تكون سجلات o2
we're going to set up two conditional statements in
فسوف نضع عبارتين شرطيتين
the join clause, both with inequalities.
في بند JOIN، وكلاهما بعدم المساواة.
First, we're going to join where o2.occurred_at is greater than o1.occurred_at.
أولاً، سنقوم بالربط حيث o2.occurred-at أكبر من o1.occurred-at.
So we're going to find orders that happened after the original order was placed.
لذا سنبحث عن الطلبات التي تمت بعد تقديم الطلب الأصلي.
And then, we're going to find orders where o2.occurred_at is less than or equal to,
ثم، سنبحث عن الطلبات حيث o2.occurred-at أقل من أو تساوي
28 days after o1.occurred_at so we're going to time bound the records.
28 يوماً بعد o1.occurred-at، أي أننا سنحدد السجلات وفقاً لوقت حدوثها.
One thing to keep in mind when doing self joins
الأمر الذي يجب تذكره عند القيام بعمليات الربط بالذات
is that you'll need to use aliases to distinguish between the left and
هو أن عليك استخدام أسماء مستعارة لتمييز الجدول الأيسر عن الأيمن
Here, again, we're using o1 and o2.
هنا، مرة أخرى، سنستخدم الاسمين o1 و o2 .